<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Footage List</string>
    <string name="addBtn">Add New Footage</string>
    <string name="seeIMDBbtn">See IMDB Page</string>
    <string name="movie">Movie</string>
    <string name="tvSeries">TV Series</string>
    <string name="alien">After a space merchant vessel receives an unknown transmission as a distress call, one of the crew is attacked by a mysterious life form and they soon realize that its life cycle has merely begun.</string>
    <string name="ash">Five friends travel to a cabin in the woods, where they unknowingly release flesh-possessing demons.</string>
    <string name="boys">A group of vigilantes set out to take down corrupt superheroes who abuse their superpowers.</string>
    <string name="crow">A man brutally murdered comes back to life as an undead avenger of his and his fiancées murder.</string>
    <string name="elm_street">A psychiatrist familiar with knife-wielding dream demon Freddy Krueger helps teens at a mental hospital battle the killer who is invading their dreams.</string>
    <string name="endgame">After the devastating events of Avengers: Infinity War (2018), the universe is in ruins. With the help of remaining allies, the Avengers assemble once more in order to reverse Thanos actions and restore balance to the universe.</string>
    <string name="fourth_kind">A thriller involving an ongoing unsolved mystery in Alaska, where one town has seen an extraordinary number of unexplained disappearances during the past 40 years and there are accusations of a federal cover up.</string>
    <string name="friday">Having revived from his wounds, Jason Voorhees takes refuge at a cabin near Crystal Lake. As a group of co-eds arrive for their vacation, Jason continues his killing spree.</string>
    <string name="hunters">In 1977, in New York City, a troubled young Jewish man bent on revenge is taken in by a secret group of Nazi hunters fighting a clandestine war against the cabal of high-ranking Nazi officials in hiding who work to create the Fourth Reich.</string>
    <string name="it">In the summer of 1989, a group of bullied kids band together to destroy a shape-shifting monster, which disguises itself as a clown and preys on the children of Derry, their small Maine town.</string>
    <string name="mando">The travels of a lone bounty hunter in the outer reaches of the galaxy, far from the authority of the New Republic.</string>
    <string name="monedas">An exiled priest tries to escape his demons while living in a remote village in Spain.</string>
    <string name="outsider">Investigators are confounded over an unspeakable crime thats been committed.</string>
    <string name="terror">Supernatural, semihistorical, horror anthology series, where each season is inspired by a different infamous or mysterious real life historical tragedy.</string>
    <string name="watchmen">Set in an alternate history where masked vigilantes are treated as outlaws, Watchmen embraces the nostalgia of the original groundbreaking graphic novel of the same name, while attempting to break new ground of its own.</string>
    <string name="wick">An ex-hit-man comes out of retirement to track down the gangsters that killed his dog and took everything from him.</string>
    <string name="xmen">The X-Men send Wolverine to the past in a desperate effort to change history and prevent an event that results in doom for both humans and mutants.</string>
    <string name="alienTitle">Alien</string>
    <string name="ashTitle">Evil Dead</string>
    <string name="boysTitle">The Boys</string>
    <string name="crowTitle">The Crow</string>
    <string name="elmTitle">Nightmare on Elm Street 3</string>
    <string name="endgameTitle">Avengers Endgame</string>
    <string name="fourthTitle">The Fourth Kind</string>
    <string name="fridayTitle">Friday the 13th 3</string>
    <string name="huntersTitle">Hunters</string>
    <string name="itTitle">It</string>
    <string name="mandoTitle">The Mandalorian</string>
    <string name="monedasTitle">30 Coins</string>
    <string name="outsiderTitle">The Outsider</string>
    <string name="terrorTitle">The Terror</string>
    <string name="watchmenTitle">Watchmen</string>
    <string name="wickTitle">John Wick</string>
    <string name="xmenTitle">X-Men days of future past</string>
    <string name="horror">horror</string>
    <string name="action">action</string>
    <string name="fantasy">fantasy</string>
    <string name="crime">crime</string>
    <string name="drama">drama</string>
    <string name="thriller">thriller</string>
    <string name="comedy">comedy</string>
    <string name="adventure">adventure</string>
    <string name="scifi">Sci-Fi</string>
</resources>